{
    "subject": "resource/Kingdom_of_Saxony",
    "predicate": "ontology/capital",
    "object": "resource/Dresden",
    "human_readable": "The capital of Kingdom of Saxony is Dresden.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9781469702720642,
            "question": "When was Dresden the capital of the Kingdom of Saxony?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9044007062911987,
            "question": "Name the capital of the Kingdom of Saxony."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9006885886192322,
            "question": "Which kingdom had Dresden as its capital city?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.849392831325531,
            "question": "What is the capital of the Kingdom of Saxony?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8020472526550293,
            "question": "Is Dresden a capital city?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6251406073570251,
            "question": "What other cities were considered as capitals of the Kingdom of Saxony?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5613651275634766,
            "question": "Where is Dresden located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5509426593780518,
            "question": "What country was the Kingdom of Saxony in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46074026823043823,
            "question": "What is the historical significance of Dresden?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.278653621673584,
            "question": "Are there any famous landmarks or attractions in Dresden?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The capital of Kingdom of Saxony is Dresden.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8802_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the historical significance of Dresden?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8802_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What country was the Kingdom of Saxony in?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8802_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where is Dresden located?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8802_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8802_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8802_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8802_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8802_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8802_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8802_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8802_80.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8802_87.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8802_9.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8802_90.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation:\n\nThe documents mention that Dresden was the capital of the Kingdom of Saxony (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_8802/re-ranker-msmarco/3.txt) and later, after 1990, it became the capital of the federal state of Saxony (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_8802/re-ranker-msmarco/25.txt). This supports the triple \"The capital of Kingdom of Saxony is Dresden.\""
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provided indeed support the statement that Dresden is the capital of the Kingdom of Saxony. Multiple texts mention Dresden's historical and current status as the capital, such as in `2.txt`, which states, \"Dresden, the capital of the Kingdom of Saxony and the residence of the royal family,\" and `47.txt`, which mentions, \"Dresden is the capital of Saxony.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}